as we go to our next game I biobot I
biobot so the standard Twitter bio these
days is usually tends to be something
like thing thing and then cookie third
thing all right it's such a predictable
formula that even spam Bots have figured
it out now they just grab photos of
unsuspecting people and just pair them
with mechanically constructed names like
this nonperson Jordan Jang Jordan Jang
not Jordan
Jordan who apparently is a meditator a
spirituality ninja and a doorman I think
a meditator would make a bad Door Man uh
this is where the computers become
self-aware it's not going to be through
the military it's going to be
spam Bots they're going to become
self-aware and then drown us out with uh
promotions for Rolexes and big dick
pills
now then they'll start playing hashtag
Wars then it's all over from there aedi
I'm going to show you a photo I want you
to give me that spam Bots Twitter bio
all right I'm going to start the clock
now first up Kimberly kimson a real
person Matt Walsh mom wolf s of
[Laughter]
[Applause]
guac all right this one Jack mcgreer
Paul stalon quilting Enthusiast
sightseer small wiener points next one
uh Michael mcgrael Banker dick pills 50%
off virus scan yeah points points next
one my favorite kennedi bumber batch uh
Jack mcer philosopher plumber beautiful
Latina
B Jer Geraldo Jack mcer milk lover poop
Soldier racist
yeah oh Jonathan
galdo points Rob rled fries Cole SLA and
a small garden salad yeah all of those
things he all those things point the
less one next one Stew French shirt stew
French shirt Matt Walsh Jonas brother
blue cheese Baldwin brother yeah
points last one desire D'Angelo Smith
Rob rle ah oh yes uh Katherine the Great
of fici
anato father of
43 and a uh glue protester yeah so
amazing we have not had one good
Catherine the Great horse joke on this
show
before